If you have configured your device to be hybrid Azure ID joined,
definitely sometimes you want to verify if every team is okay because if you are working for a big company,
it may definitely go wrong sometimes that a user calls in and says that it's having issues with the device,
so you need to verify if that device is hybrid Azure ID joined as you can totally see here.
So you can see that most of the device are hybrid Azure ID joined.
So right now to verify if your device is actually hybrid Azure ID joined,
because the device needs to be joined to your Azure Active Directory before it will be joined to your MDM or Microsoft Intune.
For example, you can see we have a device which is totally a personal device,
which is about neural fucent, you can see that the money by Microsoft Intune and all the other devices are not money by Intune.
So if I go to let me try to open CMD as an administrator and just run as an administrator.
And then I'm going to select yes.
So if I enter the following command, which is called the sregcmd/stutters.
So this is going to give all the status of the device, if the device you can see here,
what you are totally interested on is the Azure ID joined.
So the Azure ID joined means that this device has been joined to Azure ID.
So this is actually not a personal device. The device belongs to the domain kelv global.
So if I switch now to this device here, let's switch to this device.
And this is actually a personal device which was also joined to Azure ID using the Microsoft Intune.
So if I have license from a personal user, so let me open the command prompt.
Let me run this as an administrator as well.
So now we will put this as a personal device which was registered to with the money by Microsoft Intune.
So when I enter the following, let me just enter the sregcmd/stutters.
So right now you can see that because this device is not hybrid Azure ID joined.
You can see, so it's not, it doesn't belong to any domain and that's that device name.
Because this is Azure ID joined is no.
No, this means that, but if I go back again to my C001, here you can see this is Azure ID registered.
It's actually different than Azure ID, the hybrid Azure ID joined.
So this means that it's actually a hybrid Azure ID joined.